SHARLIA LEE

CONTACI



lee.sharlia@gmail.com

EDUCATION

CHEMISTRY Howard University

2004 - 2009

AGILE DEVELOPMENT WITH RUBY ON RAILS UC Berkeley; EDX.org May – Aug 2016

SKILLS

LANGUAGES

HTML, CSS, LESS/SASS, JavaScript,
JQuery, Ajax, REST APIs, Ruby, Rails, Jekyll

DESIGN

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Sketch, UXPin

COMPUTER

Word, Excel, Access, PPT, Sharepoint

SOFTWARE

Concur, Sabre, CVENT, Survey Monkey, Salesforce, Asana, Basecamp, Slack, Wordpress, Drupal

EXTRAS

Women Who Code DC – Member, Front End Developer

BlackGirlsCode DC— Tech/Parent Volunteer

BUILD Metro DC- Youth Business Mentor

ABOUT ME

I'm a Front End Developer with a specialty in event marketing and business management. I have been programming and developing websites for over four years now. I am looking for a position to use my project management skills towards technical projects.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT END DEVELOPER

STUDIO ORO LLC | JAN. 2012 - CURRENT | ARLINGTON, VA

Consultant, provides web development and IT systems support to multiple clients.

- Proficient in HTML, CSS, LESS/SASS, JavaScript, JQuery, Ajax, APIs, Ruby, Rails, Jekyll, Git, Github, CMS, and open source applications
- Provides system support setting up local networks, VPNs, adjusting firewalls, and asset maintenance

LOGISTICS COORDINATOR

NATIONAL SCIENCE FOUNDATION | OCT. 2015 - CURRENT | ARLINGTON, VA

Specializes in meeting travel expense reimbursements and reporting. Assists with event marketing and digital web needs. Concur, Sabre, CVENT, Wordpress, and Sharepoint used daily.

 Developed (2) custom websites for the NSF SBIR program conferences and workshop meetings

EVENT MANAGER

FOREST CITY ENTERPRISES | FEB. 2014 - FEB. 2015 | WASHINGTON, DC

Contract event manager for short-term retailed focused event, "Fashion Yards" Managed and oversaw all logistics and assisted with marketing the event. Successfully ran event for three seasons.

FOUNDER/CMO

STREET BOUTIQUE FASHION TRUCK | NOV. 2013 - JUL. 2015 | WASHINGTON, DC

Opened mobile retail store after successful fund raising. Developed digital marketing strategies. Coordinated and event and in-store marketing strategies + implementation. Facilitated numerous partnerships with local businesses. Received over 30 national and international press write-ups for innovative start-up company.

MARKETING DIRECTOR

CIRCE OF ALEXANDRIA INC | DEC. 2007 - APRIL 2012 | ALEXANDRIA, VA

Provided in-store support for all internal and external marketing strategies. Helped develop new partnerships with local business through PR-driven events. Created, and conducted routine sales trainings for staff. Served as interim Project Manager, for a year during salon reconstruction.

References provided upon request.

CONNECT

Github - https://github.com/lee-sharlia Codepen - http://codepen.io/Liali_dc/# Heroku (*Personal App*) - https://about-lia.herokuapp.com/ Portfolio Website - https://liacb4c.myportfolio.com/